Finding Aid for the Kenneth Macgowan Papers LSC.0887
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Additional Material (), June 1966
  - Behind The Screen: The History and Technique of the Motion Picture
    - Books Used as Research Material for the Work
      - Books used in research for Behind the screen.... v.p., v.d.; 6 items. (Box 79)
      - Pamphlets used in research for Behind the screen......, 3 items. (Box 79)
    - Material Used for Illustrations, Much of it as Returned from the Publisher
      - Material used for illustrations for Behind the screen.... including notes, ephemera and photographs., ca. 250 items. (Box 80, Folder 1-9)
    - Metal Plates of Illustrations for the Work
      - Metal plates of illustrations for Behind the screen......., ca. 20 items. (Box 81)
  - [Miscellaneous Additional Material]
    - Correspondence of Kenneth Macgowan, 1950's-1960's. (Box 82)
    - Correspondence of Kenneth Macgowan, 1920's-1950's. (Box 83)
    - Correspondence, clippings, screenplay to Young Mr. Lincoln. (Box 84)
    - Correspondence, articles by Kenneth Macgowan, material concerning the Macgowan estate, 1950-1967. (Box 85)
    - Drafts of articles by Kenneth Macgowan. (Box 86)
    - Correspondence and clippings, 1950's. (Box 87)
    - Correspondence, theater programs, lectures, account books for the Greenwich Village Theater and the Provincetown Playhouse, 1925-26 (Box 88)
    - Inserts and printed matter used in Lloyd's of London prepared for Kenneth Macgowan. London[?], v.d.; 79 sheets. (Oversize-box 89)
    - Material used for illustrations for Behind the screen.... v.p., v.d., gathered together approximately in, 1963.; ca. 100 items. (Oversize-box 89)
    - Photos for Early man in the new world. (Oversize-box 89)